[{"answer": " This is some of the finest filigreed platinum I've ever seen. But the stones, no. They're not diamonds, Mrs. my friend", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Glass will cut glass, Mrs. my friend. Do you know where it was purchased", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I can't. I just left home", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I am in school", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What happened to your hand", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I can take care of my own bills, my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Your what", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What the fuck are you doin with a son", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " That's right. Take a little, leave a little", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " You're a thousand percent right", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " I'll sign that affidavit", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You already went back to work", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " What", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Working the what", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "The tap. What you do for a living", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You're on the grift. Same as me", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "It was beautiful. And getting better all the time", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " It is, my friend! And now, right now, it's the perfect time, the best time since I've been in the game", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend, next time, couldn't Mister Hebbing", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh, I know, I know, and you've been wonderful since I was widowed. But Mister Hebbing ha", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Where", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Upstate where", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " ) The track? Did you run into my friend", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "She didn't see you, in other words", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "At what", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " A job? I've never had a legit job in my life", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend isn't after you! my friend's after me, and he's goddamn good! But so am I. I'm a survivor, my friend. I survive", "docId": "Grifters_Westlake.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "And to survive, my way, I need money. my friend knows about the stash in the car, so I didn't dare touch it, not if my friend's dead. So that leaves this", "qsentId": 28}]